Center for Inspired Teaching 'Real World History' Oral History Project 194
People's Archive, MLK Library
- Series 6: 2019-2020 School Year
  - Sub-series 3: Transcripts, 2019-2020
    - Thelma D. Jones transcript, 2019-11-27; rwhc_ohp_2019_004_tra.pdf; Jones, Thelma D., 1952-; Rogin, Lola
  - Sub-series 4: Images, 2019-2020
    - Claudia Lewis and Michael Artemus during interview, 2019-11-25; rwhc_ohp_2019_007_image.jpg; Oral history interview subject Claudia Lewis poses with her interviewer Michael Artemus, then a high school student at IDEA Public Charter School.
    - Deacon Clarence Haywood interview image, 2020-01-05
      Image of Deacon Clarence Haywood taken during his oral history interview session.
      Haywood, Clarence, Deacon, 1974-
    - Jacqueline Hines and Kiara Bellamy, 2019-11-13
      Interviewee Jacqueline Hines and her interviewer Kiarra Bellamy, a high school student from Woodrow Wilson High School enrolled in the Real World History Class.
      Hines, Jacqueline, 1954-; Bellamy, Kiarra
    - Trejure McLean and Bernice Pitts, 2020-01-07; rwhc_ohp_2019_005.jpg; From left to right Trejure McLean poses with her grandmother Bernice Pitts during an oral history interview. At the time Trejure McLean was a high school student at IDEA Public Charter School, enrolled in the Real World History Class.